oh well would you look at that they just
got a new shipment in of your favorite
cereal senior raisin bran oh come on not
that again
we already had raisin bran for like the
past three weeks yet when is it going to
be Mannix turn to pick out this cereal
you always let Sonia pick just cause
she's your favorite oh now you boys know
that that is not true yes it is mama
that's why we are getting raisin bran
aren't we of course sweetie you don't
have to worry about a thing but I want
triple chocolate chunky puffs and I want
cool-kid crisps you know what I ain't
got time for this [ __ ] I got a go get a
can of sloppy joe mix for tonight's
dinner you kids choose which cereal you
want amongst yourselves
meet me up front when you are done Oh
Charles I thought you were on the other
side of the store buying porn magazines
us you host what done it hi Uncle Chuck
we are trying to decide what area we
want what cereal do you think we should
get Oprah middle don't pray I mean what
do kids they see their own if you know
it whatever you want
know what is the slope yo Nick sweet Oh
well I was actually just on my way to
that
yes piojo Stone Emirati marriage whether
it's terribly ho a mix not one adult Oh
Feeny
what get up with resume on it says yo
alright we can get whatever we want you
know what that means it's cool-kid
Christmas it is like hell we are getting
cool kid crisps mama said we can only
get one so we are getting triple
chocolate chunky puffs you really wanna
go bro
I do I really do Sonic Manic stop
fighting if you don't stop fighting
aisle aisle
[Music]
you
hey [ __ ] don't think I didn't see you
just now you thought you were being real
sneaky just now don't you well I Got
News for you [ __ ] saw everything every
single thing I swear it should be
illegal to go outside with that crap ton
amount of makeup on your face like oh my
God you look like a [ __ ] clown whose
birthday party are you supposed to be at
wait a minute those big-ass boobs those
bloated lips that [ __ ] up ass I
remember you you're Mannix girlfriend
aren't you Mindy was it I don't have to
tell you [ __ ]
ha you won't be saying that when I rat
you out to the employee you [ __ ] just
right you will tick of [ __ ] by the time
you'll get someone I'll already be
hauling ass out of the store oh really
now you call me miss is there something
I can help you with ah [ __ ]
hey lady don't I know you from somewhere
do you seem awfully familiar um no I
don't think we've ever met each other
but I remember now
you're that [ __ ] who ran over my little
brother's bike he's in the hospital
right now
because of you I should kick your ass
right here now Charlie you and I both
know I'm not the one at fault your
brother is the one who drove up my
driveway into my garage and smacked into
my car you know what I've had enough of
your [ __ ] get out of the store right
now what but I'm the one who called you
over up fine whatever what do you want
well this [ __ ] right here just shoved
like 50 bucks worth of makeup into her
bra
up oh whoa my hello miss you've got
you've got such big boobs I'm sorry if I
sound a tad nervous it's just that I've
never met someone with such big boobies
oh no need for you to be so nervous
especially with those muscles oh man I'm
gonna spank your ass [ __ ] yeah you like
that [ __ ] yet [ __ ] shake your cute
little ass for Dad I think I might as
well tell you right now that she's
currently dating my son well your son
had better back off easy there Charlie
we maybe didn't but still lets me have
my fun that's good cause I was afraid I
was gonna have to kick his ass
okay so should I just go get the manager
and tell them what's going on because
you clearly have no idea how to do your
job all right fine
whatever you want to see me do my
[ __ ] job I'll do my job all right you
sexy [ __ ] if you shake your boobies for
me I may just let you off with the
warning
[Music]
you [ __ ] trying to win with sex appeal
you ain't the only one here with boobs
what the hell do you think you're doing
you old sack of [ __ ] how dare you even
think about comparing your saggy ass
boobs to my woman well you were just oh
my God God damn what the hell is going
on over here
oh hey Knox fancy seeing you here we're
just buying some cereal well yeah I can
see that I mean why Sonia on the ground
crying like a [ __ ] baby it's be is
because we all want a different cereal
but Nana's mom said she said we can only
get one I want cool kids crisp
I want raisin bran and I want triple
chocolate chunky puffs
triple chocolate chunky puffs you know
that [ __ ] is like 10,000 calories a
serving right
seriously I heard about this kid who
fell into a coma after having just two
bowls of that [ __ ] oh my God
they have c3 peels oh man this [ __ ] is
bitchin
I can't believe they actually got this
oh yeah and about your problem why not
just get a combo pack combo pack yet
like that one right up there those are
the three you want aren't they
we did did subs we finally decided on
what we want let's go let mom know
I'm really sorry for the wait my
children should be here any minute now
there you kids are what took you through
so long oh well I guess it doesn't
really met now that you're here
so which cereal did you pick out
we got all three
oh hell no I told you but is we could
only get one you think were made of
money
I don't think so [ __ ] I should beat
your ass right now I knew we shouldn't
have even come here oh my God Sonic is
so fat no wonder you wanted three
instead of one
[ __ ] fattest like God damn you
actually think all combo pack is worth
that amount of money [ __ ] [ __ ] it
come on we're going home right now this
is what happens when you mess with me
[ __ ] we are here so portal please
watch your footing as you step out of
the limo
oh yes Thank You Alfred remind me to
give you a fifty thousand bill once we
get back
sir excuse me sir down here sir I don't
want to be a bother
I really don't but but my parents are
dead and I'm so hungry I haven't eaten
for so long
anything you can give me anything at all
would help a ton how dare you
a poor person such as yourself has no
right to touch someone like me now I
have to burn these who knows what kind
of poor man's disease you could have
infected them with oh gee I'm so
terribly sorry I know it's not much but
here is every single thing that I own if
you want I can give you this now and one
day when I'm older and I have more money
I promise to pay you back for your pants
huh that's cute you actually think your
life is worth more than my pants I'll
give you five seconds to haul ass right
oh I didn't see you there my bitch today
what's wrong Beach why do you look so
down
Bart levy Oh Bart levy it's because my
mom wouldn't let me get my favorite
cereal
I just loved triple chocolate chunky
puffs so much that I I know now no need
to cry they're my little bitch daddy
doesn't like to see his [ __ ] cry after
all I already bought you a box so Mindy
were you able to find what you needed
yes daddy thank you for bringing me here
today you're the best they didn't tell
you were here babe Charlie I said quit
slapping my [ __ ] ass Oh Manic baby I
didn't notice it with you
damn you're looking fine today not as
fine as your big-ass boobs sugar tits oh
yeah you want some cereal Bart let me
just possum and said we could all have
as much as we want I suppose I will have
one bald I haven't eaten anything all
week since I was on my diet hold up
did somebody say cereal give me some of
that [ __ ] hey bro over there
it's Knuckles we should ask him if he
wants some cereal - yo Knuckles Bartleby
bought some cereal for everybody we were
wondering if you want some too after all
you did try to help us a little while
ago consider this and so thanks umm okay
then whatever soup Elena so we ate to
open a salon he to Toki Toto test or
tell where a host so money porn magazine
esta T wanted booty host :
Josie intend a host blue Toyota man put
the money on your car that's we know it
your route oh yeah that's perfectly fine
Charles oh by the way you want some
cereal
everyone's having some yeah yeah lay it
on a woman wait a very uni Loco birthday
it's the message plant tomahto vans
serve
gasps this but see you here holy [ __ ]
Damon's 1 2 3 4 5 s energy is so
powerful I feel like I'm going to be
blown away you stupid [ __ ]
run away everyone knows not to stand too
close at Amer's 1 2 3 4 5 his love for
Sonic Underground is so powerful he can
sometimes manifest into a physical aura
that is powerful enough to rip even time
and space apart oh my God
[Music]
haha wolf sound Mindy sometimes I just
forget my own trying it's all right team
eyes no harm done
besides I love showing my boobs to
people hey Tamers we're all getting
ready to eat cereal together would you
like a bowl cereal why thank you very
much I would love that
nothing beats Ameer between France
[Music]
you